우린 복제인간이야
누군가의 실험물이고놈들은 우릴 죽여 없에고 있어!
우린 불법 실험에실험용 쥐 같은 신세지
사라, 이러는 동안에폴은 어디있었어?
베스가 그를 감시하고있었던거 같에
지금이 폴이 일하는 곳을확인해봐야 할 때인가봐
베스 일로얘기 좀 해야겠네
감시자로서간섭하면 안된다는
자네 역할을이해하도록 하게
폴이 날 쫓아서키아라를 봤어
너도 미생물학 맞지?
델피네야
코지마야
Enchant?만나서 반갑다
나도 어쩜 감시자하고자고 있을지도 모르지
도니, 상자에뭐가 있는데?!
나도 좀 사생활이있어야지
앨리슨, 그만 못해!
"왕가슴 숨결"?!
다른 일이 또 생기면알려드리죠
감시장비로부탁해요
"유모캠"이라고불리는거죠
사라, 난 니가죽은 줄 알았어! 아-아!
돈 갖다 드릴께요형님, 아-아!
파우치가내 손가락을 가져갔지
저 돈 원해?당장 챙겨 나가
베스는 어딨지?
그 애 자살했어
내가 그 애 신분을챙겼지
너가 걔 감시자잖아아니야? 의사들이 와서
그 애가 잠든 동안의학 실험을 했지
왜인지만 말해줘
우리한텐 왜인지말 안해주거든
말도안돼!이런!
이걸 다 내가해야되는거야?
세시간 남았는데여지껏
설거지도 안했고
음료수 통도안채워져 있고
애들 선물 봉지들도정리되있지 않고
우리 얼음이나있기나 해?
여보세요우리 얼음 있어?
앨리슨, 빨리!
일정 맞춰야지이것봐
우리 서둘러야 겠어
한밤중에 어디갔었던거야, 도니?
어, 모르겠는데"네버네버랜드"?(피터팬 사는 곳)
나 깼는데당신 침대에 없더라
여보, 우리이럴 시간 없거든
애들이 밖에서뭘하고 있는지도 모르겠는데
해야될 일은 백만가지고당신은 도움도 안되고!
우리가 필요한거목록이나 적어놔
내가 망할 얼음가지러가면서 할께
당신 어디갔었는지알아야겠어, 도니
저기, 어제 우리가안좋게 보내긴 했지
안좋게 보내?
당신한텐그게 그런거야?
어디가는거야?
나가서 당신이어제 가져다 놓기로
했었던 것들을가져와야지!
난 당신하고대화를
시도하려는데도니
그러셔, 오어유 즐거워라
걱정마, 여보나중에 확실히
얘기할꺼니까그게 좋잖아
Orphan Black 01x06Variations Under DomesticationOriginal Air Date May 4, 2013
한글자막 : Nike Plus
내 문제는
군에 있을 때시작된게 아니야
군복을 벗고부터시작됐지
개별 계약직으로일하면서
이해가?
이런거 원해서했던건 아니야
좋아, 그럼, 2년동안억지로 베스의
감시자 노릇을 했는데왜인지는 전혀 몰랐던거네
너도 무슨사기꾼 같은거잖아
영향력 같은게
어떤지 알잖아그치?
차이점이라면넌 베스 생활에
침입해서는그녀의 남자친구와
바로 이 조리대 위에서뒹굴었다는거지
근데 넌너 자신도 아니였잖아
또 너도너 자신은 아니였지
넌 이 일이 얼마나심각한건지 이해하지
못하고 있는거 같은데
우리 서로한테좀 솔직해보도록
할 필요가 있겠네쌍둥이 언니
좋아
그럼 니가 나한테했었던
의학 실험에 결과는어떻게 됐어?
난 널 거기서빼내고 싶었었어
리오 가는거진심이였거든
실험 결과가 어떻게됐는지만 말해줄레?
올리비에에게들어가
거기서부터는나도 몰라
뭐하는 거지?
샤워 좀 해야겠어
더러운거씼어내야지
그래도 괜찮지?
그럼 실험 결과에내가 베스가
아니라고나왔있을꺼 같에?
그 실험이 뭐하는 건지는나도 몰라
설명했듯이내 쪽 세계가 그래, 사라
내가 신경쓰는건바로 너야
그래?
니가 나에 대해신경쓰는게 뭔데?
그게 뭐던간에 나한테얘기하진 않을꺼잖아
사라
안녕, 코지마네가 맞았어..
폴은 복제인간 같은건전혀 모르더라고
그치?이중 눈속임이라고..
감시자는 실험의
목적에 대해알지 못한다고
그런식이여야 결과에영향을 못미치거든
아, 안녕어쨌거나 나와야 했어
지금은 내가어디 가는지도 모르겠다
그렇겠다저기, 나도
감시자 딜레마가있거든
이번 학기는나도 여기가 처음이라
나랑 어울리는사람이 없었는데
누가 친구가 되고싶어하거든
사람들한테떨어져있어, 코즈
과학에만매달려있어, 알았어?
과학에만매달려있으라고?
지금, 내가 뭔데괴짜 원숭이?
심각하다고! 폴이나쁜 자식이란 말야. 알았어?
전직 군인이야
누군가 너와 가까워지려고한다면은
떨어져 있어야해
맞다, 옛말대로 "내 말대로만 해내가 하는대로 하진 마"네?
미안..
저기, 앨리슨이전화한다
우리 다 된거지
그래
헤이
나 좀 도와줘
무슨 일 있어?
음, 상황이 좀 생겼어
어떤 상황인데?
그냥 이쪽으로 와지금 바로
머야 불공평해!
어, 그럼 내가너 또 잡은거다, 하!
그만, 그만, 너동생이랑 앤슬리네 집에
가라. 너희 거기서있을꺼야
그래도, 엄마!
그래, 아주 재밌을꺼다!
싫어요! / 가! 아줌마한테다 됐다고 얘기해
어디로 뜨시려고사라?
앨리슨?
내가 왜 의자에묶여있는거지?
상자에 뭐가 있었는지솔직히 말해, 도니
뭐?
당신의 특별한 상자
그 안에 뭐가있었냐고?
당신 정신 나갔어?
풀어줘
안돼!
도니, 이 질문에
꼭 대답을들어야겠어
왜 그래, 앨리슨무슨 미친 짓이야!
걱정은 마, 여보
괜찮을 꺼야
당신이 늘 나한테하는 말 아니던가?
당신이 정말로털어놓고
싶은게 뭔지떠올려봐
아니면 뭐..
내 몸에 빤짝이라도붙여주려고?
서류 옮겼잖아
서류?무슨 서류?
나에 대해 기록한서류 말야
당신 상자에 있던당신의 특별한 상자
당신 정신 나갔어?!
당신이 한 짓 알아도니!
뭐?내가 뭐 했는데?
감시했지내가 잠들어 있을 때
의료 검사를 하고..뭐?!
내 삶 전부를 크고당혹스러운 거짓말로 만들어버렸지
그리고는 그 특별한 상자에서류들을
포르노DVD랑바꿔치기 했잖아
왕!
가슴!
숨결!
제발, 그만해
안녕, 델피네
안녕 봉쥬르코지마
지루해
그럼 말이지내가 오늘
가보려고 했던강연이 있는데
잠깐, 어딨지?내가 가려던게..
네가 나랑가고 싶다면야..
신진화론(neo+evolution-신조어)
진짜로?
너..너도 들어봤어?
그래, 이거 좀 비주륜데그렇지 않아?
머 내 생각엔
다윈주의자로써너한테 흥미로울 꺼야
거기다 여기리키 박사 말야
진짜 정말로흥미롭게 강연하거든
이 사람 테드토크인터넷에서 보고.. 뿅
*TED Talk(www.ted.com)새로운정보를공유하는온라인강연사이트
그럼?
가자
까지껏!
사라오늘 아침에 뛰쳐나간거
나도 이해해그래도 내..
우리 아래 있는
근본은 확실하다는 걸알아야지
그러니, 부탁인데..
오늘 저녁에전부 얘기해보자
왜 그런거야도니?
앨리슨, 난 당신 잘때실험같은거 안했어
오, 안돼, 안돼
나도 아픈거야?독일애처럼?
독일이 뭐?독일앤 누군데?!
안돼, 안돼!
도대체 어떻게 된거야앨리슨?
쉿!
제발, 안돼
뭐하는 거야?
제발..아
애리슨, 아돼!
도라와!
어이, 뭐가그리 급한데?
아마도 너 앉는게좋을거 같다
어, 서있을께고마워
그럼야
애리슨! 애리슨?
저건 누구야?
도니
도니가 누군데?
내 남편이야
뭐야?!
내 감시자가저 이인거 같다고!
세상에나, 앨리슨!뭔짓을 한거니?
우~후~!
계세요?!
저건 누구야?
완전 까먹고있었네
오, 파티 준비가아직 안됐나 보네
어, 그래, 음..
옷도 챙겨입지않고 있잖아
저기, 방금 생각한건데우리 장소를 바꾸면 안될까?
장소를 바꾼다고?앨리, 뭐 문제있어?
아니야, 그냥..내가 몸이 좀 안좋아서
우리가 장소를..
머, 그건 지금너무 늦었거든
그냥 진정제나 좀 먹어내가 도와줄께
걱정마, 파티는알아서 시작할께
알았어
어때요, 헨드릭스?
어서와요, 안녕!안녕!
이거 잠옷 파티였어?
끝내주네
앨리준비도 안됐네
어, 알아나 좀 봐줘
알았어
제한구역은또 뭐래?
음! 지하실말야완전 엉망이야
도니가 이번주부터개조하기 시작했거든
저기, 애들이 과자달라고외치고 있거든
내가 창고에서뭐 좀 가져올께
소세지롤이냉장고에 있어
알았어좋아
파티라고, 진짜로?진짜야
좋아, 그럼 다내쫓아버려
월 정기 파티를날려버릴 순 없거든
내 차례야
근데, 선물 상자도 없고얼음도 없어
거기다 바텐더도 없고왜냐면..
내 남편이 의자에묶여있으니까
앨리슨, 너 심호흡좀 해야겠다
요가 싫거든
그럼, 넌 올라가서주인답게
아무일 없는 것처럼행동해
알았어
넌 도니를 심문해
뭐?
그래너 전문가잖아
들어가서
거짓말쟁이 호로자식한테자백을 받아내라고
머..너 진심이야?
내가 되봐이거 입고
그냥 네 남편이면어쩌려고?
사라, 이번엔네가 날 도와줘야겠어
나 네 딸 앞에서
네 흉내를냈었거든
이번엔, 네 차례야
골프채로 말야?
안돼, 안돼나 바텐더 못해
여기 아주 잘생긴손님이 계시거든
제발 말인데
너 또 그 영안실 직원이랑같이 있는건 아니지?
아니야그럴 계획은 있지만서도
잠깐만
테디
그게 자기 전부야?
알았어보아하니 방금
오후에 시간이나겠네
좋아, 얼마나빨리 올 수 있어?
스카베리아까지?(스카보로우+시베리아)
그래, 수수하게입고와
방금 그거 농담이지?
나도 알아. 나도내 자매 짓하는거 질린다
얼음 잊지말고
이건 됐고
애들이 선물 봉지를찾고 있거든
거기다 와인잔도다 떨어졌어
일회용 컵은어디다 둬?
싱크대 밑에 있어아니다, 찬장 위에
가스렌지 위왼쪽이야
모르겠다모르겠어
아래층엔무슨 일 있어?
소세지롤 줘?
아니, 괜찮아그럼..?
미라는자기네 업자
이름을 알고싶은거야
나중에 연락처 줄께
그럼 됐네
좋아, 소세지?
아니됐어, 괜찮아
저이 벌써 취한거야?
누가 여기다의자를 갖다놨지?
다른건 필요하신거?
근데 도니는어디간거지?
안녕, 도니
안녕, 도니도니
애리스ㅇ?
안녕, 도니
앨리슨
쉬, 쉬, 쉬!
이제 그만하자제발
그러지
질문만 몇개 하고
그 여자 괜찮다고어제 말했잖나
곧바로 어두운 면을드러내더군요, 올리비에 씨
어제 밤에 그녀가약 복용하는걸 중단시켰습니다
경찰도 그만뒀고상담도 때려쳤죠
주변에 아무도없습니다
자네가 있지
다른 때처럼 이런 어려움을나눌 수 있지
정말 중요하지 않으면간섭하지 말게나
그녀가 또다시 이러면제 탓으로
돌리시지 않을지알아야겠습니다
제가 막지 못했을 때요
자넨 우릴 위해잘해줬네, 폴
자네 대상물이자기 자신의 선택을 하는 동안엔
다른 결론을내리지는 않을껄세
됐나?
그럼 임무로돌아가게
나도 알아, 도니
그러니 어떻게 된건지말해도 괜찮아
뭐가 어떻게 되는데?
이중 눈속임이나감시하는거나
앨리슨, 너 자신이무슨 말 하는지 알어?
내가 한밤 중에일어난건
크리켓 본거야!
크리켓?
남아프리카 경기는새벽 4시에 시작한다고
내 생활에서당신한테
확인받지 않은게있기나 한거야?
당장 빌어먹을눈가리개나 풀어!
동네 사람들전부 와있는거야?
당신 머리 속에도대체 얼마나
말도 안되는게들어있는거야?
어이, 말 조심해도니!
앨리슨당신 생리통에
정신 나간거 아니야?!
어이!말 조심하라고!
니 마누라가 이 가정을지탱하는거라고!
좋은 말씀은그만 하시지!
알아 들어?!
네
코지마!
왔구나
그래
와줘서 정말 고마워
절대 실망 안할꺼야
그래, 그렇겠다
그래, 리키 박사는다양한 사상에 대해
관심이 많거든이리와
그래
신진화..
내일을 위한오늘의 철학이며
과거에 뿌리를 둔
인간이란 유기체의진화입니다
하지만, 우리가미래를 둘러보기 전에
여러분을 3000년 전으로안내해 드리죠
위대한 그리스 철학자플라토의
황혼기로 말입니다
늙고 초라해진 플라토는눈이 멀어가고..
다리를 절었으며
귀가 멀어져갔습니다!
이제, 상상해 보시죠만약 우리가
그의 시력을 고쳐주고귀를 듣게 해주며
아픈 부분을티타늄 부품으로
교체해 줄 수 있다는걸알았다면
플라토는 우리를 신이라여겼을 것입니다!
하지만 아니죠. 우리는 그저근본적으로 결함을 가진
인간일 뿐입니다
당신의 안경이
예를 들자면요당신을 어떻게 좀..
음
플라토닉하게보이게 해주죠
하지만 아주 가까운미래에는
당신이 안경을 벗은 채로는이전에 결코
볼 수 없었던 빛을
볼 수 있는 능력을선사해드릴 수 있습니다..
적외선, X선
자외선까지흥미롭지 않으세요?
그냥 간단히 라식 수술부터해볼지도요
그렇게 해도 좋고요
바로 진화적인 선택을하는거죠
신진화는 우리에게자기유도적인 진화의
기회를 제공하며또한 저는
그것이 단 하나의선택이 아니라
인간의 권리라믿습니다
오, 필릭스필릭스, 필릭스
다 왔다, 필릭스
파티와 함께파티할 시간이지
오, 젠장
너 완전 앨리슨인줄알았잖아
너 거울이나봐봤어?
머리 위에뭐가 있다
망할, 사람들 말대로완전히 옆길로 샌거지, 피
필요한게 뭐야?
크래커
뭐?!
크래커좀 더 있냐고?
내가 알아야 되는거야범생언니?
찬장에 크래커 있는지직접 보시지 그래?
앨리슨
미라가 말인데도니 어딨어?
오, 이런 세상에
남편이 너 도와주지않고 뭐한데?
그이 묶여 있어
앨리, 이런데도남편 감싸주는거야?
그러지마특히 나한텐
채드랑 나 어땠었는지너도 알잖아
헤이, 숙녀분들!알았어
저기 온다
제가 그쭉 빠진 몸매에빠져있는데요
요즘 다시 둔근(엉덩이근육)을단련하고 계세요?
운동방법이뭐에요?
왜 다들 나한테 계속망할 질문을 퍼붓는거야?
안녕하세요이웃 여러분!
바텐더가도착했습니다
주최하신 분과 제가간단히
말씀을 나눠야겠군요그리고 바로 돌아오죠
어.. 당신한테요
괜찮죠?가시죠
게이 바텐더네꽤 멋진데
채드, 당신 멍청한 입 좀닥치고 애들이나 먹여
안돼
오, 이런
내가 망쳤지아니야?
도니 아닌거지그치?
그이가 아니야
그래도 후려쳤을 땐꽤 기분이 좋았어
진짜 저안에있는거야?
그래, 의자에묶여있어
오, 세상에나
알았어, 난 위에 가서엉망된거나 처리하지
내 남편을 고문하고
내 가족을 망쳤어
그리고 네가
내가 얘기할 수 있는유일한 사람이야
넌 또다른 모습의나 이니까
그만해
난 끔찍한 사람이야
난 진짜 사람도아니지
당연히너 사람이거든
이봐, 지금까지이 모든 걸 견뎌왔잖아
앨리슨, 도니 말로는한밤중에 깬건
크리켓 경기 보려고했던거레
크리켓?
그래
저기, 폴은 군인이이야전문가라고
넌 도니를 계속알았잖아, 언제부터지?
고등학교야
그렇지, 고등학교거봐
그런 사람이 어떻게감시자가 되겠어?
그럼 그냥 도니네
먹으면 방구끼는도닌거지?
내 감시자는아마도
위에 있는 잡년들중에 하나일꺼야
이봐, 앨리슨그냥..
앨리슨?!
알았어. 알아, 알았다고됐다고
아니 아니, 신진화는우생학이 아니야
그래, 그럼 뭔데?이상주의인가?
신이상주의일까나?
코지마오, 세상에, 저봐
저기 계셔
그냥 한번만나뵀으면 좋겠다
왜 그래
그러면
뭐야?
안녕하세요안녕하세요
절 반대하는분이시군요
네
프랑스어 하는군요
네. 머리에언어인식 신경칩을 박았죠
웃기세요
좋아요회의론자시라
신경회로 주입이우리가
탐구하고 있는부분이긴 해요
다이아드 연구소죠
들어보셨군요예
저분들도 다이아드 연구소에서오신건가요?
아, 저의"괴상한 리키들" 이죠
언론에서 그렇게불리곤 합니다
한번은 이런 요청이있었죠
내가 생각하는 완벽한 인간이어떻게 생겼냐고요
그때 즉석해서제안했던게
은발 머리에
눈 한쪽만하얀거였죠
저도 몰랐어요
저, 강연아주 재밌었어요
오, 감사합니다감사해요
전 면역학을하고 있거든요
음, 당신은요?
진발요, 그러다보니누가 미래에 대해서
얘기할 때면항상 대답해 주는게
"보여줘, 말로만 말고"죠
저에게 그럴 기회를주시기를 바라죠
부탁이니, 다이아드의저희 연구를 한번 봐보세요
잘가요
버르장머리 하고는
안돼!
어서, 여기서 나가자빨리와!
앨리슨
샤블리 병 또 어딨어?(프랑스 화이트와인)
나라고, 피
오, 망할미안
긴급상황이야앨리슨이 완전 쓰러졌어
안돼
우리가 이 불바다에서그앨 구해줘야돼, 어떻게든
좋아, 들어봐어쩌면 내가
진짜 감시자를점 찍었는지도 몰라
뭐?
저 쪽
여깄었네
나 여깄지
뭔 일 있는거야?
헨드릭스!오! 저기!
그런거 재밌어하는사람 없거든, 채드
후, 후, 진정해!엉덩이 좀 출렁인거 뿐이잖아
당신 전에본적 있는데요
플라자에서일하지 않아요?
하!플라자 같은거 안하거든요
어, 둘은 서로어떻게 아는거에요?
아, 음, 그게..
이 사람은, 어..
제가 연기를가르치거든요
필릭스에요
앤즐리에요길건너에 살죠
너 한번도 나한테전문적인 강습을
받는다는 얘긴안했었잖아, 앨리
진짜? 흠
앤즐리
레드가 좋아요화이트가 좋아요?
어떻게 생각해세요?
너 정말 빨리 뛴다다 따돌린 걸까?
그럼! 좋아 그럼자전거를 훔치는거야
오, 안돼, 안돼, 안돼그런 범죄는 나한테 너무 과해
오, 왜 그래
나 교직 과정도듣는단 말야
아, 그래알았어
너 진짜 프랑스 식은어떤건지 알아?
뭔데?
이렇게조깅하고 나면
작고 끝내주는 담배를피는 걸 즐기지
너 방금 "조깅"이랬어?
그래
그랬지, 알았어그냥 물어본거
너도 피워?하나 피울레?
아니, 난한텐마리화나가 좋아
우, 정말?
그럼, 나야 샌프란시스코서와서 말야..
날 잡아서 너완전히 구워줄께
좋지, 날 잡아
알았어
그게, 음..
친구 사귀는거진짜 좋다
완전 새로운 세상이야
그래
나 가야돼
그렇지, 그래
그래
안녕
잘가 안녕
도니, 자기야
내 정말전부 잘못했어
앨리슨
제발 풀어줘
안돼파티 끝날때 까지만
멀드와인도 사놨는데*뱅쇼의 영국식-와인에 알콜을 없에고 향료를 추가
내가 도와주면..
당신이여기 있는 동안
우리가 정말 어떤지생각해줬으면 좋겠어
우리가 가진거..
이 집이나우리 아이들 말야
당신도 잃고싶지 않잖아
이거 진짜 너한테잘어울린다
예?
너 윗층으로올라봐야겠어, 당장
뭐 잘못됐어?
빅이 여깄어
빅?
그래
안녕, 사라
너 올라오지 않으면
내가 친구들을 만들기시작할거야, 아주 빨리
알았어, 좋아
아래층은 안돼
위층 침실로가2분만
베스
상처가 없네
사라
너 사라 맞아?
앨리슨
이런 거원하는거야?
나랑 침대로 가자
아우! 젠장!
안좋다고!
이 망할 것좀 봐바
후!
유모차랑 우유, 거기다날 속이기까지 했지
5초 줄께, 빅오, 그래? 아님 어쩔꺼
동네 방범에전화라도 거시려고?
방범 아저씨!
헤이, 헤이목소리 좀 낮춰
너랑 나 일이마무리가 안됐잖아
앉아
그러니까
너 스스로죽은걸로 속이고선..
새로 사기칠 건으로넘어올 수 있었던거야, 응?
이번엔 누구야사라?
사라, 이거 진짜로헷갈릴텐데
넌 상상도 못할껄
너 니 돈 받았잖아빅, 그러니 좀..
5천 쥐꼬리만한걸로내 손가락이나
내 고통과 시달린덴모자르지
무슨 추잡한 짓을 하던지나도 떼줘
아니면 내가 확 니 비밀을폭로해 버릴테니까
이 껀은 그냥 두자알았지?
뭐가 있겠어?
애들 좀 봐, 헤이!
우리 애들이될 수도 있지
방 잘못찾아왔어, 형씨
당신이 빅이군
그래넌 누군데?
에, 에, 네가상관할게 아니거든
내가 너한테말했어?!
워 워 워 워
이번엔 이 여자가뭐했는데?
아, 사라, 사라, 사라
이봐, 이 여잔 나랑 일하거든나한테 얘기하시지
어, 그래그게 그런거지?
우아어, 빅
워, 워, 됐어좋아, 뒤로 돌아
뒤로 돌라고!
돈 위로 들고
원하는게 뭐야빅?
사라랑 나 일이마무리가 안됐거든
이 놀이에서내 몫을 원한다고
세금징수원이지
이 와중에 우리가제대로 한건지 니가 알아?
그거야 알거든
낚시 줄에고래가 걸린거지
그럼 누가 오기전에
다른데로 장소를 옮기지차고에서 떠들어 보자고
빅
좋아둘이 먼저 가
어, 앨리얘기 좀 할까?
실례지만, 부인들어와서 얘기하시죠
아니 아니 아니..
우리끼리 할께앨리슨
앨리슨
저건 누구야?
어, 어..어느쪽?
불가능하게 잘생긴 쪽이지뻔한 얘길
아, 대학때부터친구야
전문대지
오, 세상에, 앨리
너 채드 얘기 지겹게들은건 아는데
어, 아냐
그 망할 자식이
또 바람을피는거 같에
천천히, 천천히
됐어, 가자고
천천히, 가시지
그만 움직여
거기 의자에앉아
계속가, 친구어서, 가, 앉아!
서있자고
널 해치려는건아니거든
자전거 교실에그 잡년 때문이야
그이 다시는 안그러겠다고맹세했었는데
사람들이 얘기해?
그이가 도니한테무슨 말 했을까?
아니
아니?
한마디도
음, 결혼이란게 전부조금씩 비밀이 있잖아
우리 모두 있지
미안해, 너랑 도니도
여러가지가있는거 아는데
응?
대학 친구라
난, 어.. 나파티에 돌아가봐야겠다
너 윗도리
뭐가?
윗도리갈아입었네
파티 시작 때랑달라
아, 애 하나가
뭐 좀흘렸었거든
애 하나가..
부억에가봐야겠어
너 행동하는게아주 이상하다
내가 밝혀내고말꺼야
뭘 원하는데?형씨, 어?
그녀에 대해 아는모두를 얘기해 주면 좋겠는데
사라 말이야?
그걸로는뭐하려는 거야?
어?
그걸로 뭘 하려는거야친구?
그녀 성이 뭐지?
매닝이야사라 매닝
쌍둥이 자매가있나?
뭐?
없어, 야. 쌍둥이없다고
걔 고아야
너 베스나앨리슨은 알어?
누구?
들어봐, 친구야진정하라고, 어?
저기
나 당신을어쩌려는건 아니거든
난 그녈사랑한다고
그녈 위해서라면미친 짓도 하지
알았어, 알았어!진정하라고, 형씨!
됐다고
진정하라고, 친구
문 닫아사라 매닝
폴
그 사람은 무슨일인지아무것도 몰라
사실이라고, 형씨맹세해. 쟤 말 들어
저 안에 쇼파에누워있는건 누구야?
이봐, 그 녀석은모른다니까!
그여자 남편은 왜의자에 묶여 있는데?
형씨 좀 들어봐. 내 맹세하는데나 아무 것도 몰라
사라, 제발 얘기 좀 해줘얘기 좀 해줘
그만 좀 하라고! 이 사람 좀말려봐! 난 모른다고!
사내자식이빅!
알았어좋아. 사내답게
네가 날
상당히 위태로운위치로 몰아넣거, 사라
이 일에서 찝찝한건남기면 안되거든
이 자식이보아하니
찝찝하게남겠어
그사람 아무것도모른다고, 폴!
이봐, 형씨
나 죽고싶지 않거든됐어?
진정하라고부탁이야, 형씨
어이, 폴?내가 다 설명해줄께
베스, 앨리슨..내가 무슨 일인지
얘기해 줄께그사람 보내줘
알았어, 이봐! 맹세하는데절대 한마디도
안할꺼야, 그럼 됐지?한 마디도
사라, 제발 뭐 좀 해봐빌어먹을!
이봐, 이봐솔직하게 얘기할께, 폴!
엄마?
잡았다, 엄마!
얘야, 얘야! 젬마, 나가자엄마..
낮잠이야?
기분이 별로좋지 않거든
됐어
너 침대로가야겠다
일어나알았어
그거야
잘했어
괜찮아저건 신경쓰지마
움직여
너랑 난여기서 끝이야, 빅
절대 돌아오지 마
사라좀 있어봐
앨리슨!
내가 방금..너 여기 날라온거야?
뭐?
방금 문자그대로널 침대에 눞혔거든
깨.. 깼거든
오, 저희 아직인사도 안했죠
전 길건너 사는앤슬리에요
당신은?
그냥 들렸어요
음
내가 말했듯이
결혼이란게 전부
조금씩 비밀이있잖아
이런건 성인끼리
일이잖아
다치는 사람도없고
음, 그거 있잖아?네가 맞다
내가 상관할 바가아니지
집에 갈 시간이네
도니
아까 내가 좀음, 이성을 잃은거..
아냐, 아니, 아니 아니내 잘못이야
당신이 맞아..
당신이 우리 가정을지탱하고 있는거야
정말 미안해
당연히 당신도알겠지만
내 특별 상자에포르노 때문이 아니지
당신 지니 뉴스밤기억나?
대학때?
어떻게 말해야할지모르겠어
어쨌든 그녀하고 한번바람을 피웠어
좋아, 두번
그래도 당신이랑 내가깨졌던 시절이야
그 후에도우리가 몇년 동안
편지를 나눴거든..
대부분은지저분한 얘기지..
쯧
그러다, 그녀가루푸스에 걸렸고
다시는 소식을듣지 못했어
루푸스 걸렸다고?
어떻게 됐는지는나도 몰라
정말 미안해난 단지 뭔가
개인적인게있었으면
했던거야뭔가..
잘못했어
마실레?
그래
말해봐
복제인간
복제인간?
머, 우린 복제-하는말을 안쓰려고 하는데
앨리슨이정한거지
하지만, 그래, 우린유전적으로 동일해
세쌍둥이가아니라
유전적동일체라고?
그래, 지금까지9명이 있어
그게 당신 일이야폴
그래서 당신이베스를 지켜보던거였지
당신은 복제인간을감시하는거야
그런건처음 만났을 때
얘기 했어야지
We're clones.
We're someone's experimentand they're killing us off!
We're like lab ratsin an illegal experiment.
Sarah, where was Paulduring all this?
We think Bethwas spying on him.
Maybe it's time to checkout where Paul works.
We need to talkabout Beth.
You understandyour role as monitor
is not to interfere.
Paul followed mestraight to Kira.
You're inmicrobiology, too?
Delphine.
Cosima.
Enchante.
I may be sleepingwith my spy as well.
Donnie, what'sin the box?!
I'm entitledto a little privacy.
Alison, stop it!
"Big Boob Blowies"?!
If anything else comesup, I'll let you know.
Surveillance,please.
They call it"the nanny cam".
Sarah, I thought youwere dead! Aaah!
I'll get you yourmoney, man. Aaah!
Pouchytook my finger.
You want that money?Take it and go, now.
Where is Beth?
She killed herself.
I tookher identity.
You're her monitor,aren't you? Doctors came
and medically examinedher in her sleep.
Just tell me why.
They don'ttell us why.
Ridiculous! God!
I got to do everythingaround here?
Three hours to go,and the dishes
still haven'tbeen washed,
the drink cart hasn'tbeen loaded up,
the kids' gift bagshaven't been sorted,
and did we evenget ice?
Hello,did we get ice?
Alison, come on!
Get with theprogram, here.
We needto get moving.
Where did you go in the middleof the night, Donnie?
Uh, I don't know,Never Never Land?
I woke up.You weren't in bed.
Honey, we don't havetime for this.
The kids are outside,doing God knows what,
we got a million things to do,and you're not helping!
Just make a listof what we need
and I'll do it when I'mout getting the damn ice.
I need to know whereyou went, Donnie.
Look, I know we hada bad day yesterday.
A bad day?
Is thatwhat you call it?
Where are you going?
I'm going outto get the stuff
that you were supposedto get yesterday!
I'm trying to have
a conversationwith you, Donnie.
And, oh,what a joy it is.
Don't worry, honey,I'm sure we'll talk
about is later.It's all good.
Uh.
Orphan Black 01x06Variations Under Domestication
Original Air Date May 4, 2013
My problems
didn't startin the military.
They startedout of uniform,
as a privatecontractor.
Understand?
I'm not doing anyof this by choice.
Right, so, they forced youto be Beth's monitor
for two years, withoutever knowing why.
You're some kindof hustler.
You understand
leverage, right?
The difference is,you chose
to infiltrate Beth'slife, to screw
her boyfriend,right on this counter.
And you weren'teven you.
And you weren'tyou, either.
I don't thinkyou understand
how serious this is.
We need to tryand be honest
with each other,twin sister.
Okay.
So what happensto the results
of the medical testsyou performed on me?
I wanted to get youaway from that.
I was seriousabout Rio.
Just tell me, whathappens to the results?
They go to Olivier.
From there,I don't know.
What are you doing?
I'm going to takea shower,
wash off the filth.
Is that okaywith you?
So do you thinkthe results
might tell themI'm not Beth?
I don't know whatthe tests are for.
I explained that.This is my world, Sarah.
It is you thatI'm worried about.
Yeah?
What is it thatworries you about me?
Whatever it is you'renot telling me.
Sarah.
Hey, Cosima,you were right...
Paul doesn't evenknow about clones.
See? It'sa double blind...
The monitor's unaware
of the purposeof the experiment.
That way, they can'tskew the results.
- Oh, hey.- I just had to get out of there.
I don't even knowwhere I'm going.
Right,well, I may have
a monitor dilemmaof my own.
I'm new herethis semester.
I didn't bringanybody with me,
but someone wantsto be friends.
Just stay awayfrom them, Cos.
Stick to the science, yeah?
"Stick to the science"?
What am I,the geek monkey, now?
Seriously! Paul'sa bad arse, okay?
He's ex-military.
If somebody's tryingto get close to you,
just stay away.
Right, the old "Do asI say, not as I do"?
Sorry.
Look, Alison'scalling through.
Are we good?
Sure.
Hey.
I need you.
What's going on?
Um, I havea situation.
What kind of situation?
Just get over hereright now.
You're it! Hey, that's not fair!
Oh, then I'llget you again. Ha!
Okay, okay, you'regoing to walk your sister
to Aynsley's house and you'regoing to stay there.
But, mom!
Yes, it'sgoing to be fun!
No! Go! Tell her Isaid it's okay.
Aah! Ooh.
Where are youoff to, Sarah?
Uh.
Alison?
Why am I tiedto the chair?
Shh! Shh!
Tell me what was reallyin the box, Donnie.
What?
Your special box.
What wasinside of it?
Are you outof your mind?
Untie me.
No!
Donnie, I have
questions thatneed answers.
Come on, Alison,is is insane!
Don't worry, honey.
It's all good.
Isn't that whatyou always tell me?
Think aboutwhat you really want
to get off your chest.
Or what,
you're going to sticksequins on me?
You moved the files.
- Files?- What files?
Your filesthat you have on me.
From your box.Your special box.
Aaah!
Ohhh!Oh ohh!
Have you lostyour mind?!
I know what you do,Donnie!
What?What do I do?
You spy. You performmedical examinations
- on me in my sleep...- What?!
You turned my whole life intoa big, embarrassing lie;
and you switchedthe files
in your special boxfor porno DVDs
of "Big BoobBlowies"!
Ohohoh!Please, no.
Ahhahaha!
Hey, Delphine.
Hey. Bonjour,Cosima.
I'm bored.
Well, you know,there's this
lecture today thatI was going to see.
Wait, where is it?I was going to,
if you wantto come with me.
Neolutionism,
really?
You've...you've heard of it?
Yeah, it's kind of fringe,don't you think?
Well I think that,
as a Darwinist,it would interest you
and this Dr. Leekie
is a really, reallyinteresting speaker.
I saw his Ted talkonline and... phew.
Hmm.
So?
Sure. Why not?
Sarah,I can understand
why you took off thismorning, but I need...
we need to know
that the groundbeneath us is solid.
So, please...
Let's talk aboutall this tonight.
Why do you do it,Donnie?
Alison, I don't examineyou in your sleep.
Oh, no, no.
Am I sick, like the German?
What German?Who's German?!
No, no, no!
What the hellis going on, Alison?
Shh!
Please, no.
What are you doing?
Please... agh.
Alison, no!
Come here!
Eh, what'sthe emergency?
Umm...
You might wantto sit down for this.
I'll stand, thanks.
Okay.
Alison? Alison?
Who's that?
Donnie.
Who's Donnie?
He's my husband.
What?!
I think he'smy watcher!
Jesus Christ, Alison!What have you done?
Yoohoo!Hello!
Who's that?
Oh.
I completely forgot.
Oh, you're not readyfor the potluck.
Oh, yeah, um...
You're not evendressed.
Well, I was just thinking.Could we change venues?
Change venues?Ally, what's wrong?
Nothing, I'm just...I think I'm coming down
with something.I think we should...
Well, it's too late now,so just take some
of your happy pillsand let me help.
Don't worry, we'll getthis party started.
Okay.
What's up, Hendrix?
Hello. Hi!Hi!
Is thisa pajama party?
Good.
Ally,nothing's ready.
Oh, I know.Cover for me.
Okay.
What's alloff-limits?
Mmm! The basement.It's a disaster.
Donnie's startingrenos this week.
- Ah.- Mm-hmm!
Well, the kids arescreaming for chips.
I'll go get somefrom the pantry.
Sausage rolls,freezer.
Got it.Okay.
♪ We could be just fine
♪ I'll tell you what I want,what I really, really want ♪
- A potluck, seriously?- Seriously.
Okay, you got tokick them out.
I can't back out ofthe monthly potluck.
It's my turn.
But I have no giftbags; No ice;
and no bartender,because
my husband is tiedto a chair.
Alison, you needto take a deep breath.
I hate yoga.
Okay, you needto go up there
and just play hostess,like nothing's wrong.
Fine.
You interrogateDonnie.
What?
Yes. You arethe expert.
Go in there
and get that lyingbastard to confess.
Wh...Are you serious?
Be me.Put this on.
What if he's justyour husband?
Sarah, I need youto help me with this.
I impersonated you
in frontof your daughter.
Now, it's your turn.
♪ I wanna  I wannaI wanna  I wanna ♪
♪ I wanna really, really,really wanna ♪
With a golf club?
No, no,I can't bar tend.
I've got a veryhandsome guest here.
Please tell me
you're not with themorgue attendant again.
No, but I plan to be.
Hang on.
Teddy,
is that allyou can handle?
All right,looks like
my afternoonjust opened up.
Okay. How sooncan you be here?
To Scarberia?
Yeah. And dresssuburban.
You've got to bejoking.
I know, it sucksto be my sister.
Don't forget the ice.
Okay.
The kids are lookingfor the gift bags.
And we're running outof wine glasses.
Where are yourdisposables?
They are under the sink.No, top shelf,
left hand sideof the stove.
I don't know.I don't know.
What's going ondownstairs?
Sausage roll?
No, thanks.So...?
Meera wants to know
the name ofyour contractor.
Oh!
I will give youhis info.
Perfect.
Okay. Sausage?
No.Okay, that's fine.
She's drunk already?
Whoopsie-whoo! Whoput that chair there?
Did you want any?
And where thehell's Donnie?
Hello, Donnie.
Hello, Donnie.Donnie.
Alison?
Ah.
Hello, Donnie.
Alison.
Shh, shh, shh!Shh!
Ah!
Can we stop now,please?
Yes.
After a fewquestions.
You told me yesterdayshe was fine.
She's right back in herdark place, Olivier.
I stopped her from OD'ingon pills last night.
She's quit the force,dumped her therapist.
She has no one else.
She has you,
to share in this crisis,like any other event.
Don't interfereunless it's critical.
I need to know thatI won't be blamed
if shetries it again,
if I can't stop her.
You done wellfor us, Paul.
As long as your subjectmakes her own choices,
there are nowrong decisions.
Yes?
Then soldier on.
I know,Donnie,
so you can tell mehow it works.
How what works?
The double blind,monitoring.
Alison, would youlisten to yourself?
I got up in the middleof the night
to watch cricket!
Cricket?
The South African gamesstart at 4:00 am.
Is there nothingin my life
left unexaminedby you?
Now take offthe GD blindfold!
The whole neighborhoodis here?
What kind ofirrational nonsense
is going throughthat head of yours?
Hey, watch your tone,Donnie!
Alison,get your frazzled,
PMS shit together!
Hey!You watch your tone!
Your wife is the rockof this family!
You will no longerspeak down to her!
Am I clear?!
Yeah.
Cosima!
Hey.
- I am so glad you came.- Mm-hmm!
You won't bedisappointed.
Yeah, I can tell.
Yeah, Dr. Leekieattracts
diverse thinkers.Come.
Okay.
Oh.
Neolution...
A philosophy of todayfor tomorrow,
rooted in our past,
in the evolutionof the human organism.
But before we goto the future,
let me take you back3,000 years,
to the great Greekphilosopher Plato
and histwilight years.
Poor old Platowas going blind...
Going lame,
and losinghis hearing!
Now, imagineif he knew
we could correcthis sight,
restore his hearing,and replace
his ailing body partswith titanium ones.
Plato would've thoughtwe were gods!
But we're not, we're justfundamentally flawed
human beings.
Your glasses,
for example,make you somewhat,
um,
platonic.
But withinthe very near future,
I'll be able to offeryou the ability
to see into a spectrum
never before seenby the naked eye...
infrared, x-rays,
ultraviolet.Are you interested?
Maybe I'll just startwith basic Lasik.
And so you should.
That's makingan evolutionary choice.
Neolution gives usthe opportunity
at a self-directedevolution
and I believe that'snot only a choice,
but a human right.
Ah, Felix,Felix, Felix.
All right, Felix,
time to partywith the party.
♪ This is how we do it ♪
Oh.
Oh, shit,
I totally thoughtyou were Alison.
Have you lookedin the mirror?
There's a thingon your head.
Shit, as they say, iscompletely sideways, Fe.
What do you need?
Crackers.
Hmm! What?!
Do you haveany crackers?
How should I know,Charity?
Why don't you checkthe cracker cupboard?
Alison.
Meera is talking.Where is Donnie?
Oh, my God.
Why isn't he helpingyou with this?
He's tied up.
Ally, don't you darecover for him,
not againand not to me.
You know what I've beengoing through with Chad.
Hey, ladies!Yes.
Incoming.
I am all over thosesexy stretchies.
You been workingyour glutes again?
What's your program?
Why is everybody asking meso many goddamn questions?!
Hello, neighbors!
Your bartender's here.
I'm just going tohave a quick word
with our hostess andthen I'm going to be
right back to, uh,top you up.
Yeah?Let's go.
It's a gay bartender.That's awesome.
Chad, shut your stupidmouth and feed the kids.
♪ All hands are in the air ♪
♪ and wave themfrom here to there ♪
♪ if you're an O.G. Mackor a wannabe player ♪
No.
Oh, no.
I screwed up,didn't I?
It's not Donnie,is it?
It's not him.
But I whacked himand it felt so good.
Is he reallyin there?
Yeah, tiedto a chair.
Oh, my God.
Okay, I'll go handlethe mess upstairs.
♪ The party's underway
I torturedmy husband,
I messed upmy family,
and you're
the only personI can talk to,
and you're justanother version of me.
Come on.
I'm a horribleperson.
I'm not evena real person.
Of course you are.
Look, you stood upto all this, so far.
Mnh,mnh mnh mnh.
Alison, Donnie saysthat he got up
in the middle of thenight to watch cricket.
Cricket?
Yeah.
Look, Paul's military.He's a professional.
You've known Donniesince, what?
High school.
Right, highschool, yeah?
So how could he beyour monitor?
So he's just Donnie,
eating,farting Donnie?
My monitoris probably one
of those bitchesupstairs.
Look, Alison,just...
Alison?!
♪ Does it like nobody does ♪
♪ this is how we do it ♪
- I know. I know, I know.- Okay
No no, Neolutionis not Eugenical.
Okay, so what is it?Is it Utopian?
Neotopian, maybe?
Cosima.Oh, my God, look.
There he is.
I would just loveto meet him.
Come on.
Okay.
What?
- Hello.- Hi.
Ah,
c'est mon adversaire.
Oui.
You speak French.
Oui. I havea neurolingual chip.
Bullshit.
Good,a skeptic.
Neural implantsare something
we're exploring,however.
At the DyadInstitute.
You've heard of us.Yes.
Are they fromthe Dyad Institute?
Ah, my"Freaky Leekies",
as they've been dubbedin the media.
It was once asked
what my perfect humanwould look like.
I offhandedlysuggested
silver-gray hair
and one white eye.
Little did I know.
Well, I enjoyed yourlecture very much.
Oh, thank youso much. Thank you.
You know,I'm in immunology.
Mm. And you?
Evo-devo, so, wheneversomebody talks
about the future,I always say
"Show, don't tell."
I hope you'll give methe chance.
Please, have a lookat our work at Dyad.
Adieu.
You are such a brat.
No!
Come on, let's getout of here. Come on!
♪ Dear, I fear we'refacing a problem ♪
♪ you love meno longer, I know ♪
Mmm!Alison.
Another pintof chablis?
It's me, Fe.
Oh, shit. Sorry.
Code red. Alison justwent down in a heap.
No.
We need to get her lifeout of the fire, somehow.
Okay. Listen,I think that
I may have spottedher real monitor.
What?
There.
There you are.
Here I am.
What is with you?
Hendrix!Oh! Hey!
Nobody finds thatfunny, Chad.
Whoa, whoa, easy! Justbouncing quarters here.
I've seen youbefore.
Do you workat the Plaza?
Ha!I don't do plazas.
Oh, how do you twoknow each other?
Oh, um, because...
He's, uh...
I'm her acting coach.
Felix.
Aynsley, fromacross the street.
You didn't tell meyou were getting
professionaltraining, Ally.
Really? Hmm.
Aynsley,
do you wantred or white?
What do you think?
Um...
♪ Love me, love me
You run so fast.Did we lose them?
Yes! Okay, so let'ssteal some bikes.
Oh, no no no, that'stoo much crime for me.
Oh, come on.
I have a classto T.A.
Oh, okay.All right.
You know what's a veryFrench thing to do?
What?
After a jogginglike this,
we like to smoke a nicelittle cigarette.
Did you say"a jogging"?
Yes.
You did. Okay,just checking.
You smoke?Do you want one?
No, just potfor me.
Ooh, really?
Yes, I'm fromSan Fran, so...
Ooh.
I am going to get youso baked one day.
Mm!
Okay, one day.
Okay.
It's, um,
it's really niceto make a friend
in the BraveNew World.
Yeah.
I have to go.
Okay, yeah.
Okay.
Ciao.
Bye. Ciao.
Donnie, sweetie,
I'm so sorryabout all this.
Alison.
Please untie me.
I can't, untilthe party's over.
I bought mulled wine.
If I can help...
While you're down here,
I want you to reallythink about us,
what we've got,
with our houseand our kids.
You don't wantto lose that.
That is a reallygood look on you.
Yeah?
You needto come upstairs, now.
What's wrong?
Vic is here.
Vic?
Yeah.
Hi, Sarah.
If you don't come upstairs,
I'm going to startmaking friends, fast.
Okay, fine.
Not downstairs.
Upstairs bedroom,2 minutes.
Beth.
No scar.
Sarah.
Oh!Are you Sarah?
Mm!
Alison.
You want someof this?
Come to bedwith me.
Ow!
Ow! Damn!
That's worse!
Ow!
Look at allthis shit.
Whoa!
A stroller and a latte andyou could even fool me.
- You have 5 seconds, Vic.- Oh, yeah? Or what,
you're going to callneighbourhood watch?
Neighbourhood watch!
Hey. Hey.Keep your voice down.
You and I haveunfinished business.
Sit.
So,
you faked your own death so...
You could move onto a new scam, hmm?
Who are you now,Sarah?
Sarah, it must beso confusing.
You have no idea.
You've got your money,Vic, and then some.
5 measly grand doesn'tcover my finger,
or my painand suffering.
Whatever this scandal,I want a cut,
or I'm going to blow yourwhole charade wide open.
Let's move thisalong, yeah?
What's it gonna take?
Look at them. Hey!
Could've beenour kids.
Got the wrongroom, pal.
You must be Vic.
Yeah.And you are?
Eh, eh, this is noneof your business.
Am I talkingto you?!
Whoa whoa whoa whoa.
What's she done,this time?
Ah, Sarah,Sarah, Sarah.
Hey, she works for me.You talk to me.
Oh, yeah,is that right?
- Whoa.- Eh, Vic.
Whoa, whoa. Okay.All right, turn around.
Turn around!
Put your hands up.
What do you want, Vic?
Sarah and I haveunfinished business.
I want a cut ofthe play.
I'm the taxman.
Can't you see we're rightin the middle of it?
I appreciate that.
Got a whaleon the line.
So can we gosomewhere else,
before someone walks in,talk out in the garage?
Vic.
Okay,after you two.
Aah!
Uh,
Ally,can we talk?
Excuse us, ma'am.You can talk inside.
No no no no...
We got this,Alison.
Alison.
Who was that?
Uh, wh-which one?
The impossibly handsomeone, obviously.
Oh, a friendfrom university.
College.
Oh, God, Ally,
I know you're sick ofhearing about Chad.
Uh, no.
I think the asshole
is havinganother affair.
Slowly, slowly.
Okay, let's go.
Slowly, let's go.
Don't move.
Sit on the chair.
Let's go, buddy.Come on, go, sit!
Let's stand.
I'm not going tohurt you.
It's that slutfrom spinning class.
After he sworehe'd never do it again.
Are people talking?
Has he said anythingto Donnie?
No.
No?
Not a word.
Um, every marriage hasits little secrets.
We all have them.
I'm sorry. I knowyou and Donnie
are going throughthings, too.
Hmm?
College friend.
I've, uh... I shouldget back to the party.
Your shirt.
What?
You've changedyour shirt
since the partystarted.
Oh, one of the kids
must've spilledsomething on it.
One of the kids.
I should get backto the kitchen.
You're actingvery strange.
I'm going to getto the bottom of it.
What do you want,man, huh?
I want you to tell meeverything about her.
About Sarah?
What are you going todo with that?
Huh?
What are you going to dowith that, buddy?
What's her last name?
Manning.Sarah Manning.
Does she havea twin sister?
What?
No, man, she doesn'thave a twin.
She's an orphan.
Do you know Bethor Alison?
Who?
Listen, buddy.Calm down, okay?
Look,
I'm not tryingto shake you down.
I'm in lovewith her.
I do crazy thingsfor her.
Okay, okay!Calm down, man!
All right.
Calm down, buddy.
Close the door,Sarah Manning.
Paul,
he doesn't have anythingto do with this.
It's true, man. I swearto God. Listen to her.
Who's the womanon the couch inside?
Look, he doesn'tknow anything!
Why is her husbandtied to a chair?
Listen man, I swear to God,I don't know anything.
Sarah, could you pleasetell him. Could you please
call him off! Could you callthis guy off! I don't know!
Be a man, Vic!
All right.Okay, I'm a man.
You are putting me
in a very precariousposition, Sarah.
I can't have any looseends with this thing.
This guy seems like
a very loose end.
He doesn't knowanything, Paul!
Look, man,
I don't want to die,all right?
Just calm down.Please, man.
Eh, Paul? I'llexplain everything.
Beth, Alison...I'll tell you
what's going on,just let him go.
Okay, look! I swear to God,I'm not going to say
a word, all right?Not one word.
Sarah can you pleasedo something, goddamn it!
Look, look, I'll behonest with you, Paul!
Mommy?
Got you, mommy!
- Hey, hey! Gemma, get out.- Mom...
Aah!
Aaaaah!
Aggghhh! Ahh!
Aaah!
Quick siesta?
I don't feelso good.
Okay.
Let's get youto bed.
- Come on.- Okay.
That's it.Whoops.
Okay.
Whoops.
It's fine.Don't worry about it.
Move.
You and meend here, Vic.
Never come back.
Sarah,wait a minute.
Alison!
I just c... did youfly down here?
What?
I literally justput you to bed.
I... I got up.
Oh. We stillhaven't met.
I'm Aynsley fromacross the street.
You're?
Just visiting.
Um,
like I said,
every marriage
has itslittle secrets.
This one's between
consenting adults.
No one gets hurt.
Um, you know what?You're right.
This is noneof my business.
Time to go home.
Ahem.
Donnie,
about my little,um, breakdown...
No. No no no,it's my fault.
You're right...
You are the rockof this family.
I'm so sorry.
Of course you knew.
It wasn't just pornin my special box.
You rememberGinny Nusbaum?
From college?
I don't know howto say this,
but she and I hadan affair once.
Okay, twice,
but you and Iwere broken up.
We traded lettersfor a few years
after it ended...
Dirty talk,mostly...
Tsk.
Then, she got Lupus
and I never heardfrom her again.
She got Lupus?
I don't know whathappened to her.
I'm so sorry.I was just trying
to hold onto something
personal,something...
I'm sorry.
Drink?
Yeah.
Talk.
Clones.
Clones?
Well, we don't usethe c-word.
That's Alison's rule.
But, yeah, we'regenetic identicals.
Not triplets,
genetic identicals.
Yeah, we count nineof us, so far.
That's whatyou do, Paul,
that's why youwere watching Beth.
You monitorhuman clones.
You should've justtold me that,
in the first place.
Tiens.
Comment va-t'il?
Bien, je crois.
Stay away from me!
I have an offerfor you.
You haveuntil midnight.
If there was a club here, don'tyou think I'd know about it?
Beth's paperwork'sa mess.
It's like she'snever done it before.
Let's get forensicsto pull the hand,
run a fresh set of prints.Art, you got to see this.
The subject isn'twho we thinks he is.
She's an imposter.
Now, make this right,Afghanistan goes away.
I can tell you havea very unique
perspective,Cosima.
She's very cheeky.
But that's whyI like her.
Detective Art Bell.
I need to talk to youabout Beth Childs.